Seeds of Yesterday is a tv movie, thriller, drama film directed by Shawn Ku.
The Sheffield family reveal and go through some home truths as
their middle child inherits the Foxworth mansion.
The family's ghosts looming over, and more tragedies
are in store as the curse lives on.
Cathy, played by Rachael Carpani.
Bart, played by James Maslow.
Christopher, played by Jason Lewis.
Cindy, played by Sammi Hanratty.
Jory, played by Anthony Konechny.
Melodie, played by Leah Gibson.
Seeds of Yesterday is a television film released on April 12, 2015,
produced by Lifetime based on the 1984 novel of the same name.
The tone is emotional and intense.